<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="aboutUs"><![CDATA[<html><head></head><body style="text-align:justify;color:black;background-color:white;"><p> American Bio-Clinical Laboratories, International was first established in 1999 at Madrigal Business Park, Ayala-Alabang, Muntinlupa City, Philippines. It was founded by a group of dedicated foreign and local medical practitioners and business executives with proven expertise in Clinical Laboratories, technical skills, and sound business strategies in USA and parts of Asia.<br/><br/> Over the years, it has grown progressively to develop into an integral part of the medical community in Metro Manila and surrounding provinces, and has provided excellent, high quality, dependable and professional services to the medical and diagnostic laboratory industry.<br/><br/>The year 2010 marks a major milestone of ABC Labs, Int&#39l. as we celebrated our 10th year Anniversary in the health industry. This milestone is capped by being the first Free- Standing Referral Laboratory in the country to be accredited for ISO 15189:2010 by the Philippine Accreditation Office of the Department of Trade and Industry (PAO-DTI).<br/><br/>ABC Labs, Int&#39l. to date, continues to live up to its goal to set the trend in the Referral Laboratory industry by providing up-to-date laboratory testing systems. The year 2011, was marked by the opening and operation of its Molecular Biology Department providing both Real-Time and Conventional methods of DNA testing (The first Free-Standing Laboratory in the country to provide such services).</p></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="contactUs"><![CDATA[<html><head></head><body style="text-align:justify;color:black;background-color:white;"><p><b>Main Laboratory</b><br/>LG 3-6 Richville Corporate Tower<br/>Madrigal Business Park<br/>Ayala-Alabang, Muntinlupa City<br/>Philippines<br/><br/><b>Telephone Nos.</b><br/>(632) 850-6288<br/>(632) 850-6289<br/><br/><b>Toll Free Nos.</b><br/>1-800-108073955<br/><br/><b>Fax Nos.</b><br/>(632) 850-6287<br/>(632) 807-9626<br/><br/>e-Mail: info@abclab.com.ph<br/>www.abclab.com.ph</p></body></html>]]></string>
</resources>