<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="aboutUs"><![CDATA[<html><head></head><body style="text-align:justify;color:black;background-color:white;"><p>American Bio-Clinical Laboratories, Inc. was first established in Los Angeles, California, USA in 1984. It was founded by a small group of dedicated scientists and business executives with unique expertise in clinical experience, technical skills, and sound business strategies. ABC Laboratories is a growing clinical laboratory serving the greater Los Angeles Metropolitan area for the past 30 years. It fulfills the requirements for the Clinical Laboratory Improvement Amendments (CLIA), participates in proficiency testing with the American Association of Bioanalysts (AAB) and College of American Pathologists (CAP), and is a member of the National Independent Laboratory Association (NILA).<br/><br/>To help accommodate growth and to ensure the highest possible level of quality service to our clients, ABC Laboratories employs only qualified staff. The true test of the strength and resiliency of any company is its people. ABC Laboratories is fortunate to have extremely loyal, hard working, and dedicated management personnel and staff. It is through the concerted effort and good team spirit of our staff that ABC Laboratories continues to thrive and prosper. We strongly believe that this extremely important facet of our organization will effectively serve all our clients for the present and in the future.<br/><br/>American Bio-Clinical Laboratories, Inc. is certified nationally and licensed by the California Department of Health Services.</p></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="contactUs"><![CDATA[<html><head></head><body style="text-align:justify;color:black;background-color:white;"><p><b>Main Laboratory</b><br/>2730 North Main Street<br/>Los Angeles, CA 90031<br/><br/><b>Telephone Nos.</b><br/>(800) 738-4285<br/>(323) 222-6688<br/><br/><b>Fax Nos.</b><br/>(323) 222-3388<br/><br/>info@abclab.com<br/>www.abclab.com</p></body></html>]]></string>
</resources>